Trust your mother's instincts.
Evil Eye is a mystery, thriller, horror film directed by Elan Dassani.
A seemingly perfect romance turns dark when a mother becomes convinced her
daughter’s new boyfriend has a sinister connection to her own past.
Usha, played by Sarita Choudhury.
Pallavi, played by Sunita Mani.
Krishnan, played by Bernard White.
Sandeep, played by Omar Maskati.
Radhika, played by Anjali Bhimani.
Kelly, played by Rachel Cora Wood.
Evil Eye is a 2020 American supernatural horror film directed by Elan and Rajeev Dassani and
written by Madhuri Shekar, based on her Audible Original audio play of the same name.
The film stars Sarita Choudhury, Sunita Mani and Omar Maskati.
It was executive produced by Jason Blum of Blumhouse Television and
Priyanka Chopra Jonas of Purple Pebble Pictures.
Evil Eye was released on October 13, 2020, by Amazon Studios, as the third
installment in the anthological Welcome to the Blumhouse film series.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.